so I'm not sure that this is a complete
solution I'm pretty confident it's not
but I do see a lot of potential for the
future if we were to take this in our
own Direction I think uh Amazon's
interactive video service has a lot of
challenges with it it's really designed
for live streaming and what we would
actually have to do is uh push our
pre-recorded videos in through a live
streaming service to have them record on
the IVs site total pain uh where I'm
hoping we can be able to go with this
eventually is uh setting up a guey to
easily edit the different components of
the video the buttons that kind of thing
without uh having to deal with the
coding and I also see the potential down
the road for us to be able to create
Dynamic buttons uh based on where the
user is coming from or uh other
variables that we might be able to
capture uh so that's
it