there's still a lot to do to get this in
any sort of publishable shape uh some of
the next things that I'm going to be
working on which may be done by the time
I share this with you I've still got to
handle how to deal with captions whether
that's timed meta tags or or how that's
set up I've got to edit the video
Dimensions I've got to get it working on
mobile as well as um desktop desktop
looks to be fine right now uh I've got
to make the buttons vertical and fix
where they're at
got to remove the play toolbar at the
bottom where it starts I'm going to
change the transparency of the buttons
add some sort of humany logo add a
loading screen and probably some other
things I can't think of right off the
top of my head and what do you want to
learn about
next